<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<software-distribution project="MinGW" home="http://mingw.org" issue="2010090600">

  <!-- File: mingw32-libarchive.xml -->

  <package-collection subsystem="mingw32">
    <download-host uri="http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/mingw/%F?download" />

    <package name="mingw32-libarchive" alias="libarchive" >
      <description lang="en" title="libarchive: library for handling various archive formats" >
        <paragraph>libarchive is a programming library that can create and read
          several different streaming archive formats, including most popular
          tar variants and several cpio formats, and ar archives. It can also
          read shar, zip, jar, and xar archives, as well as ISO9660 CDROM
          images.  It automatically handles gzip, bzip2, compress, xz, and lzma
          compression and decompression, as well as uudecode decompression. The
          bsdtar program is an implementation of tar(1) that is built on top of
          libarchive.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>This MinGW port of libarchive differs from the MSYS version
          also provided by the MinGW/MSYS project.  This version does not
          require the MSYS runtime library, but does not support MSYS "unix"
          style pathnames nor mtree data.  It does not support archives that
          contain symbolic links. Both mingw32-libarchive and msys-libarchive
          (and their associated bsdtar and bsdcpio subpackages) depend on
          additional DLLs such as mingw32-liblzma (msys-liblzma), etc.  There
          is, in addition, a MinGW package that provides a standalone version of
          bsdtar which has no external dependencies and only limited
          functionality: mingw32-basic-bsdtar (see its documentation for more
          information).
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>The mingw32-libarchive package provides the runtime library,
          development files, and documentation for libarchive.  The associated
          mingw32-bsdtar package provides an implementation of tar(1) based on
          libarchive, while the associated mingw32-bsdcpio package provides a
          similar implementation of cpio(1).
        </paragraph>
      </description>

      <licence tarname="libarchive-%-mingw32-%-lic.tar" />
      <source tarname="libarchive-%-mingw32-%-src.tar" />

      <component class="doc">
        <release tarname="libarchive-2.8.3-1-mingw32-doc.tar.bz2" />
      </component>

      <component class="lic">
        <release tarname="libarchive-2.8.3-1-mingw32-lic.tar.bz2" />
      </component>

      <component class="dev">
        <requires eq="mingw32-bzip2-*-mingw32-*-dev.tar" />
        <requires eq="mingw32-libexpat-*-mingw32-*-dev.tar" />
        <requires eq="mingw32-liblzma-*-mingw32-*-dev.tar" />
        <requires eq="mingw32-libz-*-mingw32-*-dev.tar" />
        <release tarname="libarchive-2.8.3-1-mingw32-dev.tar.bz2" >
          <requires eq="mingw32-libarchive-%-mingw32-%-dll-2.tar" />
        </release>
      </component>

      <component class="dll">
        <release tarname="libarchive-2.8.3-1-mingw32-dll-2.tar.bz2" >
          <requires eq="mingw32-libbz2-*-mingw32-*-dll-2.tar" />
          <requires eq="mingw32-libexpat-*-mingw32-*-dll-1.tar" />
          <requires eq="mingw32-liblzma-*-mingw32-*-dll-1.tar" />
          <requires eq="mingw32-libz-*-mingw32-*-dll.tar" />
        </release>
      </component>
    </package>

    <package name="mingw32-bsdtar" alias="bsdtar" >
      <description lang="en" title="bsdtar: BSD version of the tar utility" >
        <paragraph>The mingw32-bsdtar package provides an implementation
          of tar(1) based on libarchive, which manipulates streaming archive
          files -- including the eponymous tar format.  However, bsdtar
          can also extract from tar, pax, cpio, zip, jar, ar, xar, and ISO 9660
          cdrom images, as well as create tar, pax, cpio, ar, and shar archives.
          It supports automatic detection and handling of .gz, .bz2, .lzma, .xz,
          and .Z decompression (and compression).  It supports ustar, pax, and
          GNU tar formats.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>This MinGW port of bsdtar differs from the MSYS version also
          provided by the MinGW/MSYS project.  This version does not require the
          MSYS runtime library, but does not support MSYS "unix" style pathnames
          nor mtree data.  It does not support archives that contain symbolic
          links.  Both mingw32-bsdtar and msys-bsdtar depend on additional DLLs
          such as mingw32-libarchive (msys-libarchive), etc.  There is, in
          addition, a MinGW package that provides a standalone version of bsdtar
          which has no external dependencies and only limited functionality:
          mingw32-basic-bsdtar (see its documentation for more information).
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>libarchive is a programming library that can create and read
          several different streaming archive formats, including most popular
          tar variants and several cpio formats, and ar archives.  It can also
          read shar, zip, jar, and xar archives, as well as ISO9660 CDROM
          images.  It automatically handles gzip, bzip2, compress, xz, and lzma
          compression and decompression, as well as uudecode decompression.  The
          bsdtar program is an implementation of tar(1) that is built on top of
          libarchive.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>The mingw32-bsdtar package provides an implementation of
          tar(1) based on libarchive, while the associated mingw32-bsdcpio
          package provides a similar implementation of cpio(1).  The associated
          mingw32-libarchive package provides the runtime library, development
          files, and documentation.
        </paragraph>
      </description>

      <licence tarname="libarchive-%-mingw32-%-lic.tar" />
      <source tarname="libarchive-%-mingw32-%-src.tar" />

      <component class="bin">
        <release tarname="bsdtar-2.8.3-1-mingw32-bin.tar.bz2" >
          <requires eq="mingw32-libarchive-%-mingw32-%-dll-2.tar" />
        </release>
      </component>
    </package>

    <package name="mingw32-bsdcpio" alias="bsdcpio" >
      <description lang="en" title="bsdcpio: BSD version of the cpio utility" >
        <paragraph>The mingw32-bsdcpio package provides an implementation of
          cpio(1) based on libarchive, which copies files between archives and
          directories.  This implementation can extract from tar, pax, cpio,
          zip, jar, ar, xar, and ISO 9660 cdrom images, as well as create tar,
          pax, cpio, ar, and shar archives.  It supports automatic detection and
          handling of .gz, .bz2, .lzma, .xz, and .Z decompression (and
          compression).  It supports the old POSIX.1 portable cpio format (odc),
          the new SVR4 portable cpio format (newc), as well as the POSIX.1 pax
          and ustar formats.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>This MinGW port of bsdcpio differs from the MSYS version also
          provided by the MinGW/MSYS project.  This version does not require the
          MSYS runtime library, but does not support MSYS "unix" style pathnames
          nor mtree data.  It does not support archives that contain symbolic
          links.  Both mingw32-bsdcpio and msys-bsdcpio depend on additional
          DLLs such as mingw32-libarchive (msys-libarchive), etc.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>libarchive is a programming library that can create and read
          several different streaming archive formats, including most popular
          tar variants and several cpio formats, and ar archives.  It can also
          read shar, zip, jar, and xar archives, as well as ISO9660 CDROM
          images.  It automatically handles gzip, bzip2, compress, xz, and lzma
          compression and decompression, as well as uudecode decompression.  The
          bsdtar program is an implementation of tar(1) that is built on top of
          libarchive.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>The mingw32-bsdcpio package provides an implementation of
          cpio(1) based on libarchive, while the associated mingw32-bsdtar
          package provides a similar implementation of tar(1).  The associated
          mingw32-libarchive package provides the runtime library, development
          files, and documentation.
        </paragraph>
      </description>

      <licence tarname="libarchive-%-mingw32-%-lic.tar" />
      <source tarname="libarchive-%-mingw32-%-src.tar" />

      <component class="bin">
        <release tarname="bsdcpio-2.8.3-1-mingw32-bin.tar.bz2" >
          <requires eq="mingw32-libarchive-%-mingw32-%-dll-2.tar" />
        </release>
      </component>
    </package>

  </package-collection>
</software-distribution>
<!-- vim: set nocompatible expandtab fileformat=unix textwidth=80 tabstop=2 shiftwidth=2: -->
