<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<software-distribution project="MinGW" home="http://mingw.org" issue="2010080900">

  <!-- File: msys-cygutils.xml -->

  <package-collection subsystem="msys">
    <download-host uri="http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/mingw/%F?download" />
    <package name="msys-cygutils">
      <description lang="en" title="cygutils (msys): A collection of simple utilities" >
        <paragraph>The cygutils package contains a collection of simple
          utilities from various sources. It provides mkshortcut and
          readshortcut, for creating and reading windows-style shortcuts.
          It provides getclip and putclip, for copying between stdin/stdout
          and the Windows clipboard. It also provides lpr-basic.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>A note about lpr-basic: lpr-basic spools a file to the
          specified printer device. MSYS provides two separate
          implementations: lpr-basic.exe and lpr-enhanced (the latter is a
          script, not a binary executable, and is available in the
          msys-lpr-enhanced package). lpr-basic.exe is suitable for most
          simple printing needs; it can send "raw" data to any installed
          Windows printer. This is most useful for raw text, for sending
          plain PostScript files to PostScript-compatible printers, and for
          re-sending .prn files generated using Windows' own print-to-file
          capabilities to the specific printer for which the .prn file was
          generated. For more information, see `man lpr-basic'. On the other
          hand, lpr-enhanced is an MSYS extension which supports many of the
          advanced capabilities of a true Unix-style lpr implementation.
          However, it is more difficult to configure. See the documentation
          embedded within the lpr-enhanced script for more information.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>The msys-cygutils package provides many of the utilities
          included in the cygutils distribution, except that the associated
          msys-cygutils-dos2unix package provides the line-ending conversion
          programs.
        </paragraph>
      </description>

      <source tarname="cygutils-%-msys-%-src.tar" />
      <licence tarname="cygutils-%-msys-%-lic.tar" />

      <component class="bin">
        <requires eq="msys-core-*-msys-*-bin.tar" />
        <release tarname="cygutils-1.3.4-4-msys-1.0.13-bin.tar.lzma">
          <requires eq="msys-libpopt-*-msys-*-dll-0.tar" />
        </release>
      </component>

      <component class="doc">
        <release tarname="cygutils-1.3.4-4-msys-1.0.13-doc.tar.lzma" />
      </component>

      <component class="lic">
        <release tarname="cygutils-1.3.4-4-msys-1.0.13-lic.tar.lzma" />
      </component>
    </package>

    <package name="msys-cygutils-dos2unix" alias="msys-dos2unix">
      <affiliate group="MSYS Base System" />
      <description lang="en" title="cygutils-dos2unix (msys): line-ending conversion utilities" >
        <paragraph>The cygutils-dos2unix package contains implementations of
          dos2unix and unix2dos (d2u, u2d) for modifying the line-ending
          character(s) used by text files. Each can operate on a list of
          files, converting them in-place, or as part of a pipeline.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>The MinGW/MSYS project provides two versions of the
          cygutils-dos2unix package: this msys-cygutils-dos2unix one, and
          the mingw32-cygutils-dos2unix version. This version requires the
          MSYS dll, but directly understands MSYS pathnames and blends more
          seamlessly into pipelines with other MSYS tools. The mingw32
          version does not require the MSYS dll, and is a direct replacement
          for the old d2u and u2d scripts, and for the unix2dos/dos2unix
          executables that were long part of the mingw-utils package.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>The msys-cygutils-dos2unix package provides the unix2dos
          and dos2unix (u2d, d2u) conversion programs. The associated
          msys-cygutils package provides other useful utilities and
          documentation.
        </paragraph>
      </description>

      <source tarname="cygutils-%-msys-%-src.tar" />
      <licence tarname="cygutils-%-msys-%-lic.tar" />

      <component class="bin">
        <requires eq="msys-core-*-msys-*-bin.tar" />
        <release tarname="cygutils-dos2unix-1.3.4-4-msys-1.0.13-bin.tar.lzma">
          <requires eq="msys-libpopt-*-msys-*-dll-0.tar" />
        </release>
      </component>
    </package>

  </package-collection>
</software-distribution>
<!-- vim: set nocompatible expandtab fileformat=unix textwidth=80 tabstop=2 shiftwidth=2: -->
