<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<software-distribution project="MinGW" home="http://mingw.org" issue="2010090600">

  <!-- File: msys-wget.xml -->

  <package-collection subsystem="msys">
    <download-host uri="http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/mingw/%F?download" />

    <package name="msys-wget">
      <description lang="en" title="wget (msys): non-interactive network downloader" >
        <paragraph>Wget is a network utility to retrieve files from the Web
          using http(s) and ftp, the two most widely used Internet
          protocols.  The program supports recursive retrieval of
          web-authoring pages as well as ftp sites -- you can use wget to
          make mirrors of archives and home pages or to travel the Web like
          a WWW robot.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>Wget works particularly well with slow or unstable
          connections by continuing to retrieve a document until the
          document is fully downloaded.  Re-getting files from where it left
          off works on servers (both http and ftp) that support it.  Both
          http and ftp retrievals can be time stamped, so wget can see if
          the remote file has changed since the last retrieval and
          automatically retrieve the new version if it has.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>The MinGW/MSYS project provides two versions of wget:
          this MSYS one supports https and understands MSYS pathnames, but
          requires the MSYS dll (and various others) to be installed.  There
          is also a 'mingwPORT' wget, which is a MinGW (that is, native
          Win32) version.  That version has no external dependencies but
          is based on an older version of wget and does not support https.
        </paragraph>
      </description>

      <licence tarname="wget-%-msys-%-lic.tar" />
      <source tarname="wget-%-msys-%-src.tar" />

      <component class="bin">
        <requires eq="msys-core-*-msys-*-bin.tar" />
        <release tarname="wget-1.12-1-msys-1.0.13-bin.tar.lzma" >
          <requires eq="msys-libopenssl-*-msys-*-dll-100.tar" />
          <requires eq="msys-libintl-*-msys-*-dll-8.tar" />
        </release>
      </component>

      <component class="lang">
        <release tarname="wget-1.12-1-msys-1.0.13-lang.tar.lzma" />
      </component>

      <component class="doc">
        <release tarname="wget-1.12-1-msys-1.0.13-doc.tar.lzma" />
      </component>

      <component class="lic">
        <release tarname="wget-1.12-1-msys-1.0.13-lic.tar.lzma" />
      </component>
    </package>

  </package-collection>
</software-distribution>
<!-- vim: set nocompatible expandtab fileformat=unix textwidth=80 tabstop=2 shiftwidth=2: -->
